A Guide to the Papers of Archie G. Richardson 1918-1976
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Literary
  - Speeches (title and no date)
    - Toward Excellence in Teaching (Box-folder 10:11)
    - The Revolution (Box-folder 10:12)
    - A Message To Parents (Box-folder 10:13)
    - An Installation Message (Box-folder 10:14)
    - Why in Service Education (Box-folder 10:15)
    - The Relationship Between the Education of the Negro,His Economic Competence (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Parents Role (Box-folder 10:17)
    - A Presentation to One Who deserves it (Box-folder 10:18)
    - Commitment to Improve Instruction (Box-folder 10:19)
    - Learning Through Experience (Box-folder 10:20)
    - Dropouts (Box-folder 10:21)
    - A Parable (Box-folder 10:22)
    - The War of Arms is ended (Box-folder 10:23)
    - A Message of Dedication (Box-folder 10:24)
    - Choosing A Carrer (Box-folder 10:25)
    - Community Leagues in Achieving Aims of Education (Box-folder 10:26)
    - Be the Best (Box-folder 10:27)
    - Youth (Box-folder 10:28)
    - Ladies and Gentlemen, Boys and Girls (Box-folder 10:29)
    - Science and Curriculum (Box-folder 10:30)
    - The Teachers Role in Pupil-Teacher Planning (Box-folder 10:31)
    - Ladies and Gentlemen (Box-folder 10:32)
    - Good Human Relations- The Foundation for A Sound Educational Program (Box-folder 10:33)
    - Better Discipline (Box-folder 10:34)
    - We Can Still See the Stars (Box-folder 10:35)
    - Why Dedicate A School (Box-folder 10:36)
    - Passing on Our Heritage (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Ways of Dealing with Children (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Education and the Foundation of Global Minds (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Working Together for Self Improvement (Box-folder 11:4)
    - A Teaches Prayer (Box-folder 11:5)
    - This Too Shall Pass Away (Box-folder 11:6)
    - The Classroom Teacher looks at Physical Education (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Developing A Schools Philosophy (Box-folder 11:8)
    - You'll find Your Problems in Your Own Back Yards (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Teacher (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Qaulity Education (Box-folder 11:11)
    - How May We Meet The Educational Needs of Children (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Decision Making in Instruction (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Strengthening the Foundatino of Democracy (Box-folder 11:14)
    - Sad Changes and The Quest for Great Ideals (Box-folder 11:15)
    - More Qaulity Needed in Education (Box-folder 11:16)
    - Youth (Box-folder 11:17)
    - The Graduate is Not to Finish When There is Work to Be Done (Box-folder 11:18)
    - Education is the Light of Life (Box-folder 11:19)
    - Art and Creativity (Box-folder 11:20)
    - Hampton Institute: Past, Present and Future (Box-folder 11:21)
    - The Soul of Man Hungers (Box-folder 11:22)
    - Recognition of Creative Ability (Box-folder 11:23)
    - Science and the Curriculum (Box-folder 11:24)
    - The Problem of Teachers, General Science in a Rural School (Box-folder 11:25)
    - Home-School-Community Teamwork (Box-folder 11:26)
    - Passing on a Heritage (Box-folder 11:27)
    - America and Education (Box-folder 11:28)
    - Teaching Today (Box-folder 11:29)
    - Status of Negro Education in Virginia (Box-folder 11:30)
    - The Importance of Efficient Leadership in the Church Today (Box-folder 11:31)
    - Education for Future Leaders (Box-folder 11:32)
    - An Awakening (Box-folder 11:33)
    - You Have Ministered To The Needs of My People (Box-folder 11:34)
    - Why the Necessity for Currculum Revision and Professional Growth (Box-folder 11:35)
    - Teaching Children to Read (Box-folder 11:36)
    - Simulation and Gaming (Box-folder 11:37)
    - Techniques of Guidance Used in Virginia Public Schools (Box-folder 11:38)
    - Parent Participation in Evaluation (Box-folder 11:39)
    - John Dewey (Box-folder 11:40)
    - Improving the Leadership Role of the Elementary School Principals (Box-folder 11:41)
    - The Characteristics of a Good School Principal (Box-folder 11:42)
    - Quo Vadis (Box-folder 11:43)
    - The Purpose of the Experiment (Box-folder 11:44)
    - For What Purpose Do We Dedicate This School (Box-folder 11:45)
    - The Elementary School (Box-folder 11:46)
    - Teaching As A Career (Box-folder 11:47)
    - The Reading Controversy (Box-folder 11:48)
    - Grouping (Box-folder 11:49)
    - Developing A School's Philosophy (Box-folder 11:50)
    - Reading in the Content Field (Box-folder 11:51)
    - The Negro In History (Box-folder 12:1)
    - There is Work to be Done (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Who is Legally Liable (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Members of the Graduating Class (Box-folder 12:4)
    - An Educational Experience (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Academic Acheivement (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Good Human Resources (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Individual Differences (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Using Test Results to Improve Instructions (Box-folder 12:9)
    - The Soul of Man Hungers (Box-folder 12:10)
    - The Teaching and Learning Process (Box-folder 12:11)
    - Learning (Box-folder 12:12)
    - Past, Present and Future of Jeans Supervision in Virginia (Box-folder 12:13)
    - Problems Encountered in the School Program to Achieve Balance (Box-folder 12:14)
    - Carver High School (Box-folder 12:15)
    - Freedom and Public Education (Box-folder 12:16)
    - Fellowships in Africa (Box-folder 12:17)
    - Education for Today's Responsibilities (Box-folder 12:18)
    - Adolescents (Box-folder 12:19)
    - What it means to be an An American Citizen (Box-folder 12:20)
    - The Land When Hate Should Die (Box-folder 12:21)
    - Creative Thinking (Box-folder 12:22)
    - Art and Learning (Box-folder 12:23)
    - Understanding Ways of Learning (Box-folder 12:24)
    - Teaching Social Studies (Box-folder 12:25)
    - Levels of Coorperation (Box-folder 12:26)
    - Why The Issue Of Integration (Box-folder 12:27)
    - The Development Of Values and Attributes (Box-folder 12:28)
    - America and Education (Box-folder 12:29)
    - The Future of Public Education for Negroes (Box-folder 12:30)
    - Facing the Parent (Box-folder 12:31)
    - Good Human Relations-The Foundation for a Sound Educational Program (Box-folder 12:32)
    - Welcome to the Mathematics Conference (Box-folder 12:33)
    - The Relationship of Health to Academic Achievement (Box-folder 12:34)
    - Human Relations in the Total School Program (Box-folder 12:35)
    - Teaching in the Space Age (Box-folder 12:36)
    - Working Together to Improve Our Schools (Box-folder 12:37)
    - The Role of the Elementary School in the Improvement of Education in Virginia (Box-folder 12:38)
    - Education and the Formation of Global Minds (Box-folder 12:39)
    - Freedom and Public (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Teachers Questions Determine the Quality of Thinking Pupils Development (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Members of the Graduation Class (Box-folder 13:3)
    - The Realities of Study Discussion Groups (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Meeting Needs of Exceptional Children (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Purpose of Summer School (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Adolescence (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Greetings to the Foreign Language Teachers (Box-folder 13:8)
    - The Activities Curriculum (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Improving the Quality of learning (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Taking Music to People Through Building Realtionships Among Academics (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Better Articulation Between the Elementary School and the High School (Box-folder 13:12)
    - The Teachers Role in Controlling Disciplinary Problems (Box-folder 13:13)
    - Teachers Questions Determine the Quality of Thinking Pupils Development (Box-folder 13:14)
    - The Roles of Principals (Box-folder 13:15)
    - The Bases of Public Education in Virginia (Box-folder 13:16)
    - Commitment to Improve Instruction (Box-folder 13:17)
    - The Teachers Role Controlling Disciplinary Problems (Box-folder 13:18)
  - Speeches (n.d.n.t)
    - N.D.N.T (Box-folder 14:1-37)
    - N.D.N.T (Box-folder 15:1-20)
  - Writings and Reports-Arranged Alphabetically
    - Autobiography (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Caroline County (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Caroline County (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Cassia School (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Conference of 1948-Study Conference 1948 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - The County Training School (Box-folder 16:6)
    - History of Mecklenburg Traning School (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Large School 1941 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Manassas Regional School (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box-folder 16:10)
    - One Room School (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Petersburg Jeanes Teachers (Box-folder 16:12)
    - Public School Transportation (Box-folder 16:13)
    - Reedy Branch Baptist Church (Box-folder 16:14)
    - Report:Mecklenburg Teachers 1931-1935 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - The Richardson Family (Box-folder 16:16)
    - The Second Mt.Zion Church (Box-folder 16:17)
    - Summary (Jeanes Supervision) 1945 (Box-folder 16:18)
    - Supervisor Workshop 1958 (Box-folder 16:19)
    - Teacher Education (Box-folder 16:20)
    - Two Teacher (Workshop) 1941 (Box-folder 16:21)
    - Union High School (Box-folder 16:22)
    - Vocational Education in Virginia 1920-1975 (Box-folder 16:23)
    - Report: Principals of Secondary Schools for Negroes Feb 1937 (Folio 16)
    - Report: Orientation and Planning Conference-Bruton Heights School June 1940 (Folio 16)
    - Report: Elementary School Principal's Workshop July 1952 (Folio 16)
    - Report:Elementary School Principal's Workshop Summer 1953 (Folio 16)
    - Report: Preparing Principals for Leadership Sept 1954 (Folio 16)
    - First Summer Conference July 1962 (Folio 16)
    - Evaluation Workshop July 1964 (Folio 16)
  - Research Notes
    - Orientation Conference Summer 1940 (Folio 17)
    - Proposed Educational Program for the Occupational and Social Needs of Negroes 1940 (Folio 17)
    - Suggestions for the Inauguration of a Twelve Year School Systems May 1947 (Folio 17)
    - A Guide for Teachers: Teaching Social Studies Spet. 1955 (Folio 17)
    - Suggested Content, Style and Format for the Preparation of Curriculum Guides Jan 1967 (Folio 17)
    - A Basic Supervisor Manual Jan 1979 (Folio 17)
    - The Core Curriculum of Virginia Secondary Schools Oct 1935 (Folio 18)
    - Program for the Revision of the Social Studies Offering for the Secondary Schools of Virginia Feb 1949 (Folio 18)
    - An Instrument for Evaluating Modern Supervisor Summer 1960 (Folio 18)
    - Curriculum Guide (Folio 18)
    - Suggestions for the Inauguration of a Twelve Year School System:Part II May 1947 (Folio 19)
    - Regional Study Groups of Supervisor and Principals on Supervision of Instruction June 1963 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Dec 1963 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Dec 1963 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log 1963 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Spring 1964 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Dec 1964 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Dec 1964 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log May 1965 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Dec 1965 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Dec 1965 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log June 1966 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log June 1967 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Spring 1968 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Spring 1969 (Folio 19)
    - The Whitcomb Court Log Spring 1970 (Folio 19)
    - Social Studies Education in Virginia Public Schools Aug 1971 (Folio 19)
    - A Preliminary Qualification Requirements for Teachers (Folio 19)
- Video Recordings
  - 3' tape Louise Archer Elementary School (Othertype 20:1)
  - 5' tape 4/25/1963 (Othertype 20:2)
  - 5' tape Speech delivered at the elementary school Principal's Conference 3/5/66 (Othertype 20:3)
  - 5' tape Andre Williams (earlier track, March 24, 1967 Ms. Pierre's class) 1967 (Othertype 20:4)
  - 5' tape Richardson Family January 1969 (Othertype 20:5)
  - Untitled (Othertype 20:6)
  - 7' tape Dr.Fred Alexander's speech 10/1/1948 (Othertype 20:7)
  - Dr.Fred Alexanders Speech continued 10/1/1948 (Othertype 20:8)
  - 7' tape "Planning a Balanced Program of Education" by Edgar G. Johnson 1961 (Folio 20:9)
  - "America and Education" by A.G. Richardson 6/12/1952 (Othertype 20:10)
  - 7' tape Massie's Mill 2/4/1955 (Othertype 20:11)
  - 7' Tape Hanover School for Boys 5/14/1955 (Othertype 20:12)
  - 7' tape Untitled 6/23/55 (Othertype 20:13)
  - 7' tape LeLaud B. Jacob's speech ACEL Conference 1961 (Othertype 20:14)
  - Richardson- Room 108 Grade 3 1961 (Folio 20:15)
  - 7' tape Dr. Ethel Alpenfels "The Challenge to Learn in a Free World" 1962 (Othertype 20:16)
  - 7' tape Whitcomb Court School; Relating Reading to other subjects 4/5/63 (Othertype 20:17)
  - 7' tape West, Clarke, Vaughn (4/25/63- Morgan and 4/5/63 Whitcomb Court School) 4/5/63 (Othertype 20:18)
  - 7' Tape Whitcomb Court School 5/21/1963 (Othertype 20:19)
  - 7' tape Dr. Simon Hampton,VA, 1964 (Othertype 20:20)
  - Erma Jean, 6/28/1966 (Othertype 20:21)
  - 7' Tape Undated- Archie Richardson Jr. (empty reel) (Othertype 20:22)
  - Instrumental Music-Beverly Thompson (Othertype 20:23)
  - 7' Tape Dr. Simon, 28 Both St., Lido Beach, N.Y. (Folio 20:24)
  - 7' tape Undated Speech at Hanover School for Boys (Folio 20:25)
  - 7' tape Undated "The Teacher" (Folio 20:26)
- Photographs and Negatives
  - Personal
    - The Valiant Volunteers-Daniel Gym 1925 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Group Outside Vawter 1926 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - V.N.I.I. vs. Hampton (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Mecklenburg County Teachers (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Mecklenburg Training School- Basketball Team 1934 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Southside Interscholastic Althetic Association 1939 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Funeral- Miss Virginia Randolph 1948 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - Workshop- First Principals Peabody 1954 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Barret School Dedication- Charles City County 1957 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - Home Economics Conference 1962 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - At Wheaton College 1965 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Art- Conference State (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Workshop Conference (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Conference at State (Box-folder 21:14)
    - Richardson's Social Activity (Box-folder 21:15)
    - Richardson's Personal Photo's (Box-folder 21:15a)
    - Richardson's Retirement (Box-folder 21:16)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 21:17)
    - Copy-School Bus (Box-folder 21:18)
    - Copy-Rosenwald School-Waynesboro (Box-folder 21:19)
    - Copy-Nansemond County (Box-folder 21:20)
    - A.G.Richardson Elementary-Blackstone (Box-folder 21:21)
    - Douglas High School- Bristol, Virginia (Box-folder 21:22)
    - Eastman 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:23)
      - Old Eastman School
    - School Bus 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:24)
      - 2 Pictures of Training School Bus
    - Tuskegee Institute 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:25)
      - Tuskegee Institute
      - Chapel Tuskegee Institute (2) 1931
      - Sen Dillard and Others-Tuskegee Institute Oct 1931
      - Statue of Booker T. Wahsington
    - Schools and Pupils 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:26)
      - Robert Stocks (2)
      - Marcelaus Rowe
      - Charles Williams
      - Mrs. Fannie Wallace
      - William Rowles
      - 18 Unidentified Pictures
    - Groups and People (Box-folder 21:27)
      - People Who benefit from the Health Clinic
      - 2 unidentified pictures
  - African American Schools in Virginia
    - Accomack County 1930-1936 (Box-folder 21:28)
      - Bayside School 1932-1933 1932-1933
      - New Accomack County H.S. 1934
      - 11th grade Accomack County Training School 1935-1936
      - Hacks Neck School
      - Doherty School
      - Quiggley School
      - New Accomack County Training School
      - Accomack County Court House
      - Central High School 1930-1931
      - Miss Forester and cooking class-Central High School 1930-1931
      - Methodist Church and Parsonage
      - Accomack County Court House
      - New County Training School
      - New Accomack Training School
      - Methodist Parsonage
      - Supt. H.A.Were
    - Albermarle County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:29)
      - 7th and 8th grade Albermarle County Training School 1930-1931
      - H.S. Group 1931-1932
      - 11th grade Albermarle County Training School 1932-1933
      - Scottsville School 1934-1935
      - E. Terry, Ivy Depot School 1934-1935
      - Ivy Depot School
      - Groups at School
      - Greenwood School (White)
      - Supt. A.L. Bernett
      - Little Billy Bernett 1932
      - Acting Supt. Ralientson
      - Faculty of Albermarle County Training School 1932-1933
      - H.S Group (8th and 9th) Esmah School 1934-1935
      - 11th grade Albermarle County Training School 1934-1935
      - Eghert Linng Ivy High School 1934-1935
      - Albermarle County
      - Hillshone School 1934-1935
    - Alleghany County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:30)
      - Dr. and Mrs. Gibbs (Clifton Forge) 1931
      - Faculty (Clifton Forge) 1931-1932
      - Alleghany County Courthouse
      - Clifton Forge Colored school
      - Alleghany County Court House (2) 1933
      - Senior Class Halston School 1934-1935
      - Wrightsville School 1935
    - Amelia County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:31)
      - Amelia County Teachers 1930-1931
      - Amelia County Court House
      - New Amelia Courthouse (2)
      - Teacher and Miss Mabel Carney Hadone School 1932-1933
      - Supt. Wigglesworth
      - James A. Green School
      - New Haven School
      - Rocky Hill School
      - Mr. Caingo and Wife 1931
      - Branch School
      - Muxillo School
      - Pleasent Grane School
    - Amherst County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:32)
      - High School Dept. 1932-1933
      - Faculty Training School 1932-1933
      - Puppy Creek School 1935
      - Trinity School 1935
      - Daniel Hill School 1935
      - Chestnut School 1935
      - Sunnyside School 1935
      - Daniel School 1935
    - Appomattox County 1927-1935 (Box-folder 21:33)
      - Appomattox Teachers 1927-1928
      - Promised Land School Child 1931-1932
      - Group At Appomattox 1932
      - Vera School 1932
      - Rev. and Mrs. Mozella Price 1932
      - New County Training School 1932
      - Wesley Chappell White School 1932
      - Teachers of 1932-1933 1932-1933
      - Faculty of 1932-1933 1932-1933
      - High School Dept 1932-1933
      - 11th grade 1933-1934
      - Spring 1934
      - Stonewall School 1934
      - Senior Class 1934-1935
      - Morning Star School 1935
      - White (Groups) 1935
      - Branen School 1935
      - Faculty of Appomattox County Training School 1932-1933
      - Spoutspring School 1934
      - Supt. and Mrs. N.R. Featherston
      - Faculty of Appomattox County Training School 1932-1933
      - Supt. Featherston
      - Supt. Burke and 2 members of the school board 1926-1927
      - Pamplin School 1932
      - Flag Exercises County Training School Feb 22 1933
      - Appomattox County Courthouse
      - Appomattox Teachers 1934-1935
      - Clerks Office
    - Arlington County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:34)
      - Teachers of Carrington School 1932-1933
      - Christian School 1934
      - Supt. of Arlington County
      - Arlington County H.S. (white)
    - Augusta County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:35)
      - Lipscomb School
      - Stuart Draft 1935
      - Cromora School
      - Rural Hill School 1935
      - Middle Grove 1935
      - Tulane School
      - Cemetary School 1934
      - Lodane School
      - Christian School 1934
    - Bath County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:36)
      - Smith Lock School Children 1931-1932
      - Colored Teachers 1931-1932
      - Milborne School
      - Training School Bus (3) 1932
      - Milboro School (2)
      - Switchback School (2) 1934-1935
      - T.C.Walker School (Milboro) (4)
      - Smithlock School 1934-1935
      - Bath County Training School- H.S.Group 1934-1935
      - T.C.Walker School (class) 1934
      - T.C.Walker School Students
      - Bath County Court House
      - Switchback School
      - Supt. D.R. Sinclair
    - Bedford County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:37)
      - Miss Hinkley and Miss Marshall 1931
      - Saunders School 1935
      - Oak Mulgre School
      - Bedford City Negro School 1932-1933
      - Mount Vale School
      - Senior Class-Training School 1934
      - New Bedford County Court House (4)
      - Hurleigh School 1934
      - Western Light School
      - Supt. W.K. Bannett
      - Supt. J.A.G. Shipley (2)
      - Unknown (illegible)
    - Bland County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:38)
      - 3rd grade Cenes School (white) 1933
      - White School
      - Cenes (4 males) 1933
      - At Cenes (Wagner,Erucham,Enoky,Slrung) 1932-1933
      - Group at Cenes (3) 1933
      - Bland County Training School 1933
    - Botetourt County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:39)
      - Training School Mauh-Botetourt County 1931-1932
      - Granel Hill School
      - Prickney School Children 1932-1933
      - 8th and 9th grades-Botetourt County Training School Feb 1934
      - Prickney School
      - Botetourt County Court House October 30
      - Botetourt County Court House (2)
      - Supt. Painter Oct 30
      - Supt. E.A. Painter
    - Brunswick County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:40)
      - Zion School
      - Piney Grace School
      - Teachers at James A. Green School
      - Mallory School
      - Brunswick County Parade of Schools
      - Green Town School
      - Burkley School
      - Miss Holmes Acting Supt.
      - Supt. Chambliss
      - Scott Lewis School
    - Buchanon County 1930-1935 (Folder 21:41)
      - County Court House 1934
      - Botetourt County Training School 1932-1933
      - Buchanon County Court House 1934
      - Mama on mule back 1934
      - group ar Hunley's School 1934
    - Campbell County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:42)
      - Church School
      - Campbell County Teachers at Thadacs School 1932
      - Hancock School 1932
      - Brookneal School 1932
      - Branley School 1932
      - Campbell County Court House
      - Brashurst White School
      - Lawson School
      - Crosley School
      - 11th grade Cambpell County Training School 1931-1932
      - Campbell County Teachers 1931-1932
      - Senior Class (11th grade) Campbell County Training School 1932-1933
      - White Hall School (3) 1935
      - Pafrant Children 1932
      - Hat Creek School
      - Hadfer School
      - Jacksontown School (3) 1935
      - Jacksontown School Agric. Building 1935
      - New School Building Acmpbell County Training School
      - Supt. and Wife
      - Campbell County Teachers 1932
      - Senior Class Campbell County Training School 1934-1938
    - Caroline County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:43)
      - 12th grade Caroline County Training School Nov 1934
      - Baltys School
      - Senior Class Caroline County Training School 1934-1935
      - Sycamore School
      - Central Parish School
      - Caroline County
      - Faculty of Caroline County Training School 1930-1931
      - 11th grade Caroline County Training School 1930-1931
      - Teachers of Lemaline Jeo 1931-1932
      - Caroline County Court House Oct 3
      - Wanepark School
      - Caroline County Court House (2)
      - Son of Supt. Vaughn
    - Carroll County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:44)
      - Carroll County Court House
      - Supt. (2)
    - Charles City County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:45)
      - 11th grade Charles City County Training School 1930-1931
      - Grand Charles City County Training School 1930-1931
      - 11th grade Charles City County Training School 1933-1934
      - Ruthville(2) 1932
      - Brumana Park- Charles City County Training School 1930-1931
      - 11th grade Charles City County Training School 1931-1932
      - Senior Class Charles City County Training School 1932-1933
      - 11th grade Charles City County Training School 1931-1932
      - Charles City County Court House
      - Supt. H.L. Harris
      - Residence 1932
    - Charlotte County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 21:46-47)
      - Nazareth School 1934